<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugh Paterson III on Hugh Paterson III for Eugene City Council</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugh Paterson III on Hugh Paterson III for Eugene City Council</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 07:30:55 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Accountability</title>
      <link>/docs/accountability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/accountability/</guid>
      <description>We can increase Accountability through an independent elected auditor Read the ballot measure 20-283. It is professional. This is the professional solution. Eugene is mature enough to benefit from an elected auditor.
We can increase Accountability by making Eugene&amp;rsquo;s transactional data open By putting Eugene&amp;rsquo;s transactional data in the open it gives citizens the capability of engage in areas of interest to them and have the same data that the city is looking at.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Land Use</title>
      <link>/docs/land-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/land-use/</guid>
      <description>We need lots of housing solutions in Eugene. There is no one size fits all solution. There is no silver bullet. We have various kinds of housing crisis in Eugene. We have chronically homeless. We have temporary homeless. We have a shortage of affordable housing for people on fixed incomes who want to own their own property. We have a shortage of housing for (lower income) students. We have a shortage of small properties for single member households.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leading Green</title>
      <link>/docs/leading-green/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/leading-green/</guid>
      <description>How will you help leading Eugene toward 100% Clean Energy by 2050? We need to work on community development strategies (especially at the city policy level) that make passive home construction practical and affordable. This needs to be part of our affordable housing plan. We also need create an economy where renewable energy solutions are the affordable solution. Right now there is a significant financial barrier, and a slow return on investment for those who pay upfront for renewable Energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Data</title>
      <link>/docs/open-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/open-data/</guid>
      <description>Open Data in context In the Eugene context of governance, citizens want to know that the city is acting fairly and in their best interests. One way to do this is to take the city&amp;rsquo;s transactional and research data and put that in the public space.
For Eugene there are two important aspects of open data: comprehension and possess-ability.
Comprehension The web is a primary means of communication for many (most) of the people living in Eugene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Run</title>
      <link>/docs/why-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/why-run/</guid>
      <description>The measure for independent Auditor sets the tone for this election. The People of Eugene expect Clarity, Openness, and a demonstration of responsibility from their elected officials and their appointed officials.
The essence of Eugene that we hold dear, be it our Eugene neighborhoods or the larger character of our city is being challenged by internal and external pressures.
The pace and scope of change in Eugene is set to increase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ward 3 debate sponsored by SUNA</title>
      <link>/blog/suna-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 07:30:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/suna-debate/</guid>
      <description>From 7-8:30 PM the three Ward 3 candidates answered questions from Citizens and Neighborhood associations. This debate was hosted by SUNA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eugene City Club Debate</title>
      <link>/blog/city-club-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 12:30:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/city-club-debate/</guid>
      <description>City Club Link: http://www.cityclubofeugene.org/events/eugene-city-council-candidate-forum-for-contested-seats/
KLCC link (listen): http://klcc.org/post/eugene-city-council-candidates-weigh-auditor-measure
Register Guard coverage: http://registerguard.com/rg/news/local/36602402-75/eugene-council-candidates-debate-merits-of-competing-auditor-ballot-measures.html.csp</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signatures Complete</title>
      <link>/blog/signing-for-candidate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 12:30:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/signing-for-candidate/</guid>
      <description> Signing the papers to get on the city Ballot </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugh Paterson III</title>
      <link>/company/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/company/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Password Recovery</title>
      <link>/password-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/password-recovery/</guid>
      <description>Your email    Send Back to Log In
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign In</title>
      <link>/account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/account/</guid>
      <description>Email   Password   Log in
Forgot password?
If you have any questions about authorization or you&#39;re our customer but haven&#39;t receive your login credentials, just send us a short email at support@company.com and we&#39;ll fix it right away.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>