<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on Hugh Paterson III for Eugene City Council</title>
    <link>/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on Hugh Paterson III for Eugene City Council</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Accountability</title>
      <link>/docs/accountability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/accountability/</guid>
      <description>We can increase Accountability through an independent elected auditor Read the ballot measure 20-283. It is professional. This is the professional solution. Eugene is mature enough to benefit from an elected auditor.
We can increase Accountability by making Eugene&amp;rsquo;s transactional data open By putting Eugene&amp;rsquo;s transactional data in the open it gives citizens the capability of engage in areas of interest to them and have the same data that the city is looking at.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Construction Exercise Tax</title>
      <link>/docs/no-cet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/no-cet/</guid>
      <description>Should Eugene implement a Construction Exercise Tax (CET )? In response to Jacob Fox and Terry McDonald who published a guest opinion in the Register Guard on April 6th 2018. It does not make sense to implement a CET in Eugene.
When we look at how the math pencils out, it would be much better for Eugene Citizens to donate to 501( c)3 organizations like St. Vincent de Paul who are making a real difference in Lane County.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Land Use</title>
      <link>/docs/land-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/land-use/</guid>
      <description>We need lots of housing solutions in Eugene. There is no one size fits all solution. There is no silver bullet. We have various kinds of housing crisis in Eugene. We have chronically homeless. We have temporary homeless. We have a shortage of affordable housing for people on fixed incomes who want to own their own property. We have a shortage of housing for (lower income) students. We have a shortage of small properties for single member households.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leading Green</title>
      <link>/docs/leading-green/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/leading-green/</guid>
      <description>No paper or plastic campaign signs Recently Hugh went to the The Glenwood Central Receiving Station. He says:
 I noticed all these political signs in the trash. It really challenged me to think about the environmental impacts of my campaign. I can run a facebook add just as much as printing signs and flyers. It has less of an impact to the environment.
 If you want a city councilor who is concerned with the environment and our social responsibility, look no further than Hugh Paterson III.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Data</title>
      <link>/docs/open-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/open-data/</guid>
      <description>Open Data in context In the Eugene context of governance, citizens want to know that the city is acting fairly and in their best interests. One way to do this is to take the city&amp;rsquo;s transactional and research data and put that in the public space.
For Eugene there are two important aspects of open data: comprehension and possess-ability.
Comprehension The web is a primary means of communication for many (most) of the people living in Eugene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Run</title>
      <link>/docs/why-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/why-run/</guid>
      <description>The measure for independent Auditor sets the tone for this election. The People of Eugene expect Clarity, Openness, and a demonstration of responsibility from their elected officials and their appointed officials.
The essence of Eugene that we hold dear, be it our Eugene neighborhoods or the larger character of our city is being challenged by internal and external pressures.
The pace and scope of change in Eugene is set to increase.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>